Phone

+92 343 326 6252

Email

muhammadjan761@gmail.com

Address

Mahmodabad Gate Karachi.

Country

Pakistan

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Univeristy of Sindh Jamshoro. 2018 - 2021

INTERMEDIATE

C&S Govt: Degree College Shikarpur. 2014 - 2016

LANGUAGES

English

Intermediate

Urdu

Fluent

Sindhi

Native

REFERENCE

Muhammad Hussain

Ast: Professor I University of Sindh T: +92 308 362 2931

Engr. Irshad Ahmed

Senior Full Stack Developer I OBHost T: +92 341 365 4580

JAN MUHAMMAD

WEBSITE DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am a passionate website developer my core expertise is in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Core PHP, Mysql Database, Wix, WordPress, and Shopify. Always at the forefront to grasp the concept and overview of modern technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021-2022 PHP DEVELOPER - INTERNSHIP LEAD TO JOB

Deevloopers | Karachi

Developed chat app, login forms with APIs (Facebook, Google, Twitter, and Linkedin) and developed websites.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Core PHP,

JQuery, MySQL and OpenGraph Liberary.

2022-Present JR. FULL STACK DEVELOPER

HBox Digital | Karachi

Worked on lots of different projects and technologies. Developed custom websites, CRM, and CMS as per client

requirements with the team.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, JQuery, Ajax, PHP, Rest APIs, Soap APIs, MySQL, Wix, Wordpress,

and Shopify.

SOFTWARE SKILL

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax

Core PHP, Laravel Oracle, MySQL, SQL

Wordpress, Shopify, Wix Rest APIs, Soap APIs

MS OFFICE 07/10/16 SEO, SMO

C++, Java, Python Visual Studio, Sublime